Hey guys, welcome to this new video
which is kind of an experiment because I received some bricks from UVMesha
and they asked me if I wanted to collaborate with them and I said yes, why not, let's try this.
I'll start right away with the first one.
I haven't even unpacked them yet.
So this is the first one. It's called Japanese Air Banks wig. I've no idea how they chose this
name. It's called Banks but that's it. I guess I have to wear something like that before, which
is a wig cap. So this is the wig cap which is supposed to hold my hair and I heard that
you have to put them on the overhead. Oh my gosh. Help me. Okay these wigs have bangs.
I think all of them have bangs so you don't see the part at the hairline.
Okay, this is a lot of hair.
I don't know.
I definitely like that it's not kind of too shiny.
So it doesn't look like fake hair at the first moment.
Which doesn't make sense because it has to be fake hair.
I think all of these wigs cost between 35 and 40 dollar and so pretty affordable and I didn't expect that quality for a price. Cheers!
so the color is definitely pretty unusual but uh i like it it's kind of pale so it gives me
pale complexion so i think uh since it's such a bright color i like to compare it with black
and this is a pvc jacket from face clothing i think it looks pretty good together
yeah and just a nice contrast with the pale blue and purple and the shiny black so I kind of feel
like a superhero with this long fluffy hair and that jacket and I didn't think that I would like
this one that much this is so cool I couldn't imagine it but I love it I don't know I can't
stop touching it. Next up is this one and it's called Golden Lolita Long Roll Wig. Seriously,
no idea how these names are being put together. But it's blonde. I've never been blonde in my life
before. Oh my god.
Okay.
I can't see anything.
There's so many hairs.
But I think this one is even longer and there are even more hair.
I kind of feel like a Barbie mermaid.
I don't know.
This is so unusual to be blonde.
It's like kind of freaking me out and I had to pair this wig with this bandage dress.
I can show you if I want to.
Still think the blue one was cooler but maybe I have to get used to the blonde stuff.
So you've been here, you witnessed it, my first time being blonde ever.
but I think now it's time to put this away and do something different.
Okay next up is the Havayuku Lolita wig with two small buns. Without that.
So I have two packages. One is wig and one is the buns.
Oh god I can't see a thing.
Wait. Hello?
Oh and there are the buns.
Okay there are some kind of hair clamps in there.
It looks like something out of Star Wars or something.
don't know it's hairy and like having a mouth I just combined this wig with a
dress with the color I think the hair length and the colors go really well
together and this is just some fake leather dress so I cut the bangs because they
kept poking into my eyes and now I don't know I've never had hair this short
and I hope I put these buns in right. I feel like one of the Glücksbärchis.
I know, but I feel totally cute. It's so amazing. I would have never thought that
some hairstyle like this would, I don't know, look that decent on me. I really like this one as well.
also the length. I thought the color would be a bit more intense according to the
pictures from home page. This one is like really pale but it fits my lipstick.
Last one. This one is called gradient long curly wig. Okay way too long bangs again
alright I just cut the bangs again like three centimeters or something and now I
can see something and there's a lot of hair and a lot of volume going on I
think the two colors are pretty cool I like them in the length I'm sure about
the different colored bangs anyway I paired it with a outfit from restyle
I love that combination with the skirt and blouse.
So now it's really witchy.
Love the combination of the color and the hat. I'm pretty
happy how this turned out as well. I think my favorite one still is the blue one, the first one,
followed by
sorry, hair,
followed by the short one and then this one and the blonde one i think if you're looking for some
affordable weeks these ones are great i didn't think so at the beginning but i totally love how
they turned out there is a discount code with my name i put them down in the description below
you can use it to get i think 10% off it's not an affiliate link um they're definitely
neat bangs because you can see the hairline and with this one there's a
huge like hair line bend here but with all this hair going on at the front no
one will notice so if you're looking for a good start with wigs like I did then
go for it so thank you you UBME for giving me this chance of trying on all
these weeks. I totally love this experience and how the different looks turn out. Thanks again. Goodbye!